Captain, we should be in this fight.
You know there'd be no point.
None of our weapons can do
any damage to those things.
We've got no choice
but to leave this to the hunters.
All of you, engage the enemy!
If they get past us, the front line
is going to collapse!
I-It's no good! We're too low-ranked
to stand a chance!
Damn it... I'm...
losing consciousness...
Healing magic?
Amazing. He healed me in an instant!
Look out!
Byung-gu, get down!
Yoonho!
Right!
It's the S-Ranks...
The S-Rank hunters are here!
You're rushing things too much, Byung-gu.
Sorry. I wanted to help
as many people as I could.
Besides, I knew you two would protect me.
I don't think that's the boss.
Probably just the leader of this swarm.
Byung-gu, look after the wounded.
I've got it covered, Yoonho!
Let's go, Eunseok!
Yes, sir!
Pure brute strength.
Guess it wasn't the leader after all.
Now this is getting fun.
It seems they made it in time.
Now then, we should get started.
Guildmaster Choi, whenever you're ready!
Right.
Commence the attack!
Over ten years ago,
a series of gates linking our world
to an alternate dimension appeared.
The other side of each gate teemed
with bizarre creatures called "magic beasts",
immune to conventional weaponry.
Those who have awakened the abilities
necessary to fight these beasts
are called hunters.
Based on the amount of magical power
contained within their bodies,
they are ranked, in descending order,
as S, A, B, C, D, or E-Rank.
However, once these powers have awakened,
no amount of individual effort
can ever result in greater strength.
Good luck with today's raid.
Thank you.
Hey, Kim!
Been a while!
Hey, if it isn't Park!
What're you doing here?
I thought you said you'd had enough hunting.
That was before my wife got
pregnant with our second kid.
Makes sense. If the raid goes well,
you'll be raking it in.
I'm pretty nervous, though.
It's been so long that I dunno
if I'm still in good enough shape.
Not like I was that strong to begin with.
Hey, it's Sung!
What's up, Sung?
Nice of you to come out despite
the chilly weather.
Good to be working with you guys again today.
Hey, Sung! You eat before coming in?
Yeah. I had a proper meal.
What's with him? Is he a big deal?
Everyone's saying hello.
The exact opposite, actually.
He joined up after you quit, and that kid...
His nickname is "The Weakest
Hunter of All Mankind."
Weakest? Not strongest?
Nope.
Like, a trip through an E-Rank gate
landed him in the hospital.
He might be the weakest hunter there is.
Out of everyone? He's that bad?
So as a rule, you can assume any raid he
gets called in for will be pretty easy-going.
I get you.
I'd hate for him to overhear us,
so let's leave it at that.
Too bad I already caught it all.
Well, can't argue with the truth.
Oh, no, Jinwoo! You're hurt again?!
Ah, Joohee... Looks like
we'll be working together again.
Never mind that. What happened to your face?
Same thing that usually
happens to it, really...
You seriously need to be more careful!
I heard you even ended up in the hospital.
It was an E-Rank dungeon,
so I was the only one hurt.
Wasn't there a healer?
Everyone else was higher-ranked, so...
they didn't think to bring a healer along.
Are you serious?!
They were only thinking of
themselves! That's awful!
It's okay. It's my fault for being so weak.
You know how it is with me, Joohee.
I'm used to it.
Looks like we're heading in already.
Come on.
I'll be your humble leader
for this raid outing.
The name's Song Chiyul.
It's a pleasure.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Mr. Song's got the most
skills out of anyone here.
It's a relief to have him in charge.
Pleasure to be working with you, Mr. Song.
All right. Is everyone ready?
Let's head in.
Hey, Sung.
Try and hang in there behind us,
and don't get injured this time.
Right.
Let's give it our best.
A knife with barely any magic power in it...
But it was all I could afford.
It's better than nothing, at least.
Today, I'm gonna see this through!
Welcome back from your meeting, Chairman Go.
How'd things go with the administration?
The usual talking points.
Dungeon breaks are a problem,
but they still want the resources that
can be collected from inside dungeons.
Their demands make logical sense.
And we hunters make a living
by selling those resources.
The stones collected from defeated beasts—
these essence stones.
They're valuable.
I did it!
I finally got one.
Jinwoo!
Stay back, Joohee!
I'm heading to the next magic beast.
Joohee, look after Sung!
Right!
You're going to be okay!
I promise I'll heal you!
The essence stones collected
from high-ranked beasts
can be turned into powerful weapons
and gear for fighting other beasts.
Mana crystals that can
be collected from dungeons
have a similar application,
but they're less potent.
But the government's
interested in a different use.
As a new power source.
Safer than nuclear, more efficient
than water, wind, or geothermal,
and one that doesn't pollute
the atmosphere like fossil fuels.
The ideal clean energy source.
They're working on a way
to generate electricity
using essence stones and mana crystals.
A rare fuel source that only
hunters are able to collect...
Which is why the duty that rests on
hunters' shoulders is such a great one.
All right!
Yes! We beat the dungeon boss!
That's Mr. Song for you!
We did it!
Jinwoo, you're not staying on as a hunter
just because you're stubborn, right?
If you keep this up, it's only a matter of time
until something much worse happens.
It's not just your midsection.
You're hurt all over!
Sorry...
I don't want an apology!
I'm worried about you!
Have you all collected your loot yet?
As much as we could, at least.
There's not much in the way of
mana crystals here, either.
We're not gonna earn much
at all, at this rate.
I guess it's over.
And all I have to show for it
is an E-Rank essence stone.
Hardly worth almost dying for.
Hey!
Take a look at this!
A cave?
Some kind of tunnel?
It seems to go pretty far.
A double dungeon, huh?
I'd heard rumors before, but...
We beat the dungeon boss,
but there's no sign of it shutting down.
Yeah, I thought that was strange.
Which means...
Yeah, there's more loot
to be found down here.
Listen up, everyone.
When encountering
unexpected cases like this,
standard procedure is to wait
for orders from the Hunter's Association.
Hang on a sec, Mr. Song...
Doesn't that mean that the new guys
are gonna hog all the good stuff?
It's still part of a D-Rank dungeon.
It should be fine, right?
He's got another kid on the way.
And we didn't find many mana crystals.
It'd be okay to bend
the rules a bit, wouldn't it?
Or no?
I understand how you feel.
But the fact remains that it'd be a risk.
Let's take a vote.
I dunno...
I'm in!
I say no.
No.
Let's check it out.
Same.
Yeah.
I don't think so.
I say we go.
Likewise.
Sorry, but... I don't want to.
That makes six in favor, six against.
You're the only one left, Sung.
What do you think?
I-I...
Even a D-Rank dungeon is dangerous for me.
But... Now that Dad's gone missing,
I'm the only one who can
provide for my family.
I need money for Mom's treatments...
and to send my sister to college.
I need this money!
Let's go.
Now, if you could touch the black
crystal with one hand, please.
Next, please.
You're a C-Rank?
We'd love you to join our guild.
Here's the contract.
You can find the labor
conditions detailed here...
Right. One B-Rank and two C-Ranks
have agreed to sign.
Things are going smoothly so far,
Guildmaster Choi.
That's wonderful to hear.
Age and gender aren't a factor.
If they seem like an asset, make an offer.
Not that we're likely to find anyone
who can compare to Cha Hae-in.
Someone! Catch them!
Out of the damn way!
Move! Or do you wanna get run over?!
E-Excuse me...
Here.
Thank you! Thank you so much!
That's Cha Hae-in!
Cha Hae-in!
The S-Rank hunter!
Oh, damn!
It's really her!
This is awesome!
I'm a huge fan!
E-Excuse me...
Can I shake your hand?
Look at her go!
That's an S-Rank hunter for you.
How long's it been since we entered the cave?
About 40 minutes.
The gate shouldn't close until an hour
after the boss is beaten,
so we'll have 20 minutes to spare.
Um... I'm sorry.
About what?
It's because I voted the way I did
that we're searching for the boss now.
You don't need to worry about me, so stop it.
Are you sure you're okay?
Of course...
I'm not!
Have you already forgotten?!
If that attack had hit just a little higher,
you'd be dead right now, Jinwoo!
I was barely able to heal your arms
and legs, too! This is insane!
Are you sure you didn't hit your head?!
Because it seems like it!
Sorry...
It's true that having a B-Rank healer like
Joohee around has saved me more than once.
Do you actually understand the problem here?
Yeah.
Well, in that case, maybe you should
treat me to show your gratitude.
Or what? You don't like the thought
of taking me out to eat?
Th-Th-That's not it at all!
We're here!
It's the boss chamber.
Rare to see an actual door on one of these.
It's kind of intimidating.
Well, I'm going in.
No way am I going back empty-handed now.
Same here. Let's do it.
The team moves onward together.
That was the call, right, Leader Song?
Yeah, you're right.
To the newly awakened: I am the chairman
of the Hunter's Association, Go Gunhee.
Among you there are bound to be those
who choose to be hunters,
and those who decide not to.
It's been over ten years
since the gates first appeared,
and yet there's still a great deal
we don't know about the dungeons.
To become a hunter is to risk your life.
Even those who have grown accustomed to raids
cannot afford to let their guards down.
You must never grow arrogant, or careless.
If you want to survive, this advice
will serve you above all else:
Please, be afraid.
Hey, the place lit up.
Dig the atmosphere!
I've never seen a dungeon like this before.
What's with the statues?
They look so old.
And some have instruments.
This one's way bigger than the rest.
Damn, that's huge.
What it supposed to be?
There's something creepy about it.
Gotta say, I'm not seeing any beasts.
Good point.
Not a single one...
What is this? A magic circle?
Mr. Song! Something's written over here!
In the ancient script? Let's take a look...
"The Commandments of the Cartenon Temple."
"First, revere God."
"Second, praise God."
Jingwoo!
"Third, prove your faith to God."
That big statue... I saw its eyes move.
It's been watching us!
"Those who do not follow these laws..."
It can't be. You must have imagined it.
"...will not leave alive"?
Hey! The door just shut!
But why?!
Are we trapped in here now?
This is what I was worried about!
You guys didn't take this seriously,
and now look!
We never should've come this way!
I'm leaving!
You can have the treasure,
or whatever else you find in here.
See ya!
Get away from there!
No!
Are you kidding me?
They moved!
Are we supposed to fight those things?!
The guy who just died...
Was he D-Rank?
If nothing else, he was stronger
than me and my E-Rank.
And he was just... in an instant...
This doesn't make sense!
This is supposed to be a D-Rank dungeon!
There shouldn't be magic beasts
like this down here!
If these statues are moving... That means...
I've stood on the precipice of death
plenty of times before.
In my first raid ever, I got separated from
everyone else, and ended up stranded.
I've been attacked by E-Rank beasts
and spent weeks in a hospital afterward.
I almost starved to death
in a labyrinth before, too.
No matter how low-ranked the dungeon was,
I was always fighting for my life.
Most hunters are able to buy gear with the
money they make from selling essence stones,
so they can beat even stronger beasts,
and reap even bigger rewards.
But this cheap knife is the best I can afford.
If it breaks, I'll have to fight empty-handed.
These shoes are done for, too.
And so, day after day...
I've endured being mocked,
and put up with a life-threatening job
where the risks outweigh the rewards.
But even then, in order to survive,
I've learned to keep my eyes open
and look for opportunities.
That might be why I was able to tell...
Everybody, get down!
What the hell?!
Nobody mentioned this!
What is going on here?!
How should I know?!
You all right?
Yeah. How about you, Kim?
I'm fine.
No more... No more!
What is happening here?
How is this possible?
We're trapped. We're done for.
We're dead. Dead.
We're gonna die!